

#36 Mahogany Drive, Woodland Park, Off Olton Trace, Arima. Contact 1-868-309-5908 18th January 1987 30 years

Objective

Offering proven track record of organizational efficiency and productivity improvements. Performance-driven administrative professional with experience in facilitating support services and office management, strong organizational, customer service and communication skills with the ability to independently plan and direct business affairs. Trusted liaison and assistant. PC Proficiency in MS Word, Excel, Power Point and proprietary software systems.

Education

*October 2014 - August 2015

School of Business and Computer Science Edexcel Higher National Diploma Graphic Design – Year I

*January -May 2013

School of Business and Computer Science
ABE QCF Level 4 Management Information System

*June -December 2008

School of Business and Computer Science ABE QCF Level 4 Business Management

*February-June 2007

School of Practical Accounting Accounting

*March-April 2005

Micro Corporate Training (MCT) Ltd Microsoft Office

*September 1999- June 2004

North Eastern CollegeMathematics 3
English A 3
Geography 2
English B 2
Food & Nutrition 2
History 3

Technical Proficiency

Windows/ MAC Microsoft Office Adobe InDesign Adobe Illustrator Adobe Photoshop

Experience

January 2009- June 2015

Ministry of National Security-Immigration Division

Immigration Operations Assistant

*Scanning of documents

Data Entry

Accuracy checking

File checking

Establishing and maintaining communication with Sub-Units and Immigration Officers Assisting Interpol Officers with Arrival & Departure information of Persons of Interest

May- November 2008

Ministry of Finance- Customs and Excise Division

Clerical Clerk

*Assisting with the preparation of Overtime Pay Sheet

Typing of Reports and Documents for the Collector, Officer in

Charge and Supervisor

Assisting with the completion of Quarterly Appraisals for all

Officers and Guards

Other clerical and registry duties

January 2007- January 2008

St Clair Medical Centre (MEDCORP)

Customer Service Representative

*To provide efficient and professional Customer Service

Pre-booking and registering patients for scheduled procedures

Entering of patients on the personal computer

Single handily ensuring the smooth running of Accident &

Emergency Department

Operation of company Console Switchboard

Completion of insurance forms, data entry, photocopying and filing of patient records

July-September 2005 Micro Corporate Training (MCT) Ltd

Tutor

*Teaching of Computer Literacy to all ages

Assisting advancing students with Peachtree

November 2004-May 2005 Hearty Foods Supermarket

Cashier

*Cashing

Hobbies

Reading, Photography, Baking, Cooking, Creating & Designing, Spending quality time with my son.

References

Denise Scanterbury

868-646-6689

Military Academy SYSP Old Teachers Training College,

Mausica Road,

D'Abadie

Latchman Rampersad

868-396-5924

Immigration Division,

67 Frederick Street,

Port of Spain